<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><title><![CDATA[موقع أبشروا]]></title><description><![CDATA[موقع أبشروا]]></description><link>https://abshiro-azhar.github.io/</link><image><url>https://abshiro-azhar.github.io/favicon.png</url><title>موقع أبشروا</title><link>https://abshiro-azhar.github.io/</link></image><generator>Ghost 4.36</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 16:53:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://abshiro-azhar.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title><![CDATA[Start here for a quick overview of everything you need to know]]></title><description><![CDATA[We've crammed the most important information to help you get started with Ghost into this one post. It's your cheat-sheet to get started, and your shortcut to advanced features.]]></description><link>https://abshiro-azhar.github.io/welcome/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6497377904235c000169a328</guid><category><![CDATA[Getting Started]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Ghost]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 18:35:42 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="https://static.ghost.org/v4.0.0/images/welcome-to-ghost.png" medium="image"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://static.ghost.org/v4.0.0/images/welcome-to-ghost.png" alt="Start here for a quick overview of everything you need to know"><p><strong>Hey there</strong>, welcome to your new home on the web! </p><p>Unlike social networks, this one is all yours. Publish your work on a custom domain, invite your audience to subscribe, send them new content by email newsletter, and offer premium subscriptions to generate sustainable recurring revenue to fund your work. </p><p>Ghost is an independent, open source app, which means you can customize absolutely everything. Inside the admin area, you&apos;ll find straightforward controls for changing themes, colors, navigation, logos and settings &#x2014; so you can set your site up just how you like it. No technical knowledge required.</p><p>If you&apos;re feeling a little more adventurous, there&apos;s really no limit to what&apos;s possible. With just a little bit of HTML and CSS you can modify or build your very own theme from scratch, or connect to Zapier to explore advanced integrations. Advanced developers can go even further and build entirely custom workflows using the Ghost API.</p><p>This level of customization means that Ghost grows with you. It&apos;s easy to get started, but there&apos;s always another level of what&apos;s possible. So, you won&apos;t find yourself outgrowing the app in a few months time and wishing you&apos;d chosen something more powerful!</p><hr><p>For now, you&apos;re probably just wondering what to do first. To help get you going as quickly as possible, we&apos;ve populated your site with starter content (like this post!) covering all the key concepts and features of the product.</p><p>You&apos;ll find an outline of all the different topics below, with links to each section so you can explore the parts that interest you most.</p><p>Once you&apos;re ready to begin publishing and want to clear out these starter posts, you can delete the &quot;Ghost&quot; staff user. Deleting an author will automatically remove all of their posts, leaving you with a clean blank canvas.</p><h2 id="your-guide-to-ghost">Your guide to Ghost</h2><ul><li><a href="https://abshiro-azhar.github.io/design/">Customizing your brand and site settings</a></li><li><a href="https://abshiro-azhar.github.io/write/">Writing &amp; managing content, an advanced guide for creators</a></li><li><a href="https://abshiro-azhar.github.io/portal/">Building your audience with subscriber signups</a></li><li><a href="https://abshiro-azhar.github.io/sell/">Selling premium memberships with recurring revenue</a></li><li><a href="https://abshiro-azhar.github.io/grow/">How to grow your business around an audience</a></li><li><a href="https://abshiro-azhar.github.io/integrations/">Setting up custom integrations and apps</a></li></ul><p>If you get through all those and you&apos;re hungry for more, you can find an extensive library of content for creators over on <a href="https://ghost.org/blog/">the Ghost blog</a>.</p><hr><h2 id="getting-help">Getting help</h2><p>If you need help, <a href="https://ghost.org/pricing/">Ghost(Pro)</a> customers can always reach our full-time support team by clicking on the <em>Ghost(Pro)</em> link inside their admin panel.</p><p>If you&apos;re a developer working with the codebase in a self-managed install, check out our <a href="https://forum.ghost.org">developer community forum</a> to chat with other users.</p><p>Have fun!</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to grow your business around an audience]]></title><description><![CDATA[A guide to collaborating with other staff users to publish, and some resources to help you with the next steps of growing your business]]></description><link>https://abshiro-azhar.github.io/grow/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6497377904235c000169a31e</guid><category><![CDATA[Getting Started]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Ghost]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 18:35:37 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="https://static.ghost.org/v4.0.0/images/admin-settings.png" medium="image"/><content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://static.ghost.org/v4.0.0/images/admin-settings.png" alt="How to grow your business around an audience"><p>As you grow, you&apos;ll probably want to start inviting team members and collaborators to your site. Ghost has a number of different user roles for your team:</p><p><strong>Contributors</strong><br>This is the base user level in Ghost. Contributors can create and edit their own draft posts, but they are unable to edit drafts of others or publish posts. Contributors are <strong>untrusted</strong> users with the most basic access to your publication.</p><p><strong>Authors</strong><br>Authors are the 2nd user level in Ghost. Authors can write, edit and publish their own posts. Authors are <strong>trusted</strong> users. If you don&apos;t trust users to be allowed to publish their own posts, they should be set as Contributors.</p><p><strong>Editors</strong><br>Editors are the 3rd user level in Ghost. Editors can do everything that an Author can do, but they can also edit and publish the posts of others - as well as their own. Editors can also invite new Contributors &amp; Authors to the site.</p><p><strong>Administrators</strong><br>The top user level in Ghost is Administrator. Again, administrators can do everything that Authors and Editors can do, but they can also edit all site settings and data, not just content. Additionally, administrators have full access to invite, manage or remove any other user of the site.<br><br><strong>The Owner</strong><br>There is only ever one owner of a Ghost site. The owner is a special user which has all the same permissions as an Administrator, but with two exceptions: The Owner can never be deleted. And in some circumstances the owner will have access to additional special settings if applicable. For example: billing details, if using <a href="https://ghost.org/pricing/"><strong>Ghost(Pro)</strong></a>.</p><blockquote><em>Ask all of your users to fill out their user profiles, including bio and social links. These will populate rich structured data for posts and generally create more opportunities for themes to fully populate their design.</em></blockquote><hr><p>If you&apos;re looking for insights, tips and reference materials to expand your content business, here&apos;s 5 top resources to get you started:</p><ul><li><a href="https://ghost.org/blog/how-to-create-a-newsletter/"><strong>How to create a premium newsletter (+ some case studies)</strong></a><strong> </strong> <br>Learn how others run successful paid email newsletter products</li><li><strong><a href="https://ghost.org/blog/membership-sites/">The ultimate guide to membership websites for creators</a></strong><br>Tips to help you build, launch and grow your new membership business</li><li><strong><a href="https://newsletterguide.org/">The Newsletter Guide</a></strong><br>A 201 guide for taking your newsletters to the next level</li><li><a href="https://ghost.org/blog/find-your-niche-creator-economy/"><strong>The proven way to find your niche, explained</strong></a><br>Find the overlap and find a monetizable niche that gets noticed</li><li><strong><a href="https://ghost.org/blog/newsletter-referral-programs/">Should you launch a referral program? </a></strong><br>Strategies for building a sustainable referral growth machine</li></ul>]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>